cacareerzone.org 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction

California CareerZone is a technology partnership between California Career Resource Network (CalCRN) and Headed2, LLC. ("Headed2"). This Privacy Policy was created in order to disclose its use of consumer data collected about you. This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 25, 2010. Any questions regarding this policy should be directed by email to [privacy@headed2.com](mailto:privacy@headed2.com). You may also contact Headed2 at P.O. Box 696, New York, New York, 10274. The following discloses Headed2's information gathering and dissemination practices for applications including those accessed through a third party website ("Applications"). If you follow a link that takes you outside of this website, you will be subject to the privacy policy and terms and conditions of the website you are visiting. 

### Information Collected and Received

Headed2 may collect or receive information about each person who uses the Applications including, but not limited to, user name, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, interests, job history and other personal information. Headed2 also collects information on the pages you access and other information you may volunteer. Headed2 does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not use the Applications or send any information about yourself to Headed2,. No one under the age of 13 may provide any personal information to Headed2. If Headed2 discovers that Headed2 has collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, Headed2 will delete that information as soon as possible. If any one believes that Headed2 has any information from or about a child under 13, please contact Headed2 immediately at [privacy@headed2.com](mailto:privacy@headed2.com). Minors 13 and older should ask their parents permission prior to sending any information about themselves through the Application. 

### Uses of Information

Except as described in this section, we will not disclose your personal information to any third party without notifying you of our intent to share the information and giving you an opportunity to prevent your information from being shared. Nothing herein will restrict us from sharing your information with CalCRN.

From time to time, we may partner with companies based on your interests. These partner companies will never see your email address or any other information that could identify you or be used to contact you directly. Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name, address or email address with a partner company will be done only with your permission.

Headed2 reserves the right to disclose information when required by law. We occasionally use other companies to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information. By contractual agreement, those companies must treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, we will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies.

The website registration form requires users to give Headed2 contact information (such as your name and email address) and demographic information (such as your zip code, age, or income level). Headed2 uses customer contact information to send the user information about Headed2 and promotional material from some of Headed2's partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. Headed2 may use demographic and/or profile data to tailor the visitor's experience on this website, show the visitor content that Headed2 thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. The demographic and profile data will be shared with advertisers ONLY on an aggregate basis.

### Security

Headed2 uses industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged between Headed2 and other companies to help ensure its security. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Headed2's control.

### Successors and Assigns

This Privacy Policy injures to the benefit of successors and assigns of Credential Consultants.

### Amendments

Headed2 may amend this policy at any time. If Headed2 is going to use personally identifiable information collected through this website in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection Headed2 will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on this website for 30 days prior to such use. This Agreement may not be otherwise amended except in a writing that specifically refers to this Privacy Policy and is physically signed by both parties.

### Contacts

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, you can contact [privacy@headed2.com](mailto:privacy@headed2.com). You can access the information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that Headed2 collects and maintains about you in your account. You can modify information previously provided by editing it in your account. 

### Opt-Out

This website will provide you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional email communications from Headed2 with instructions in the applicable promotional email.
